Daniel Walder

Computer Engineering & Cognitive Science

Contact

Phone (619) 629-5735

E-mail

dwalder@ucsd.edu

Personal Website

www.danielwalder.website

Skills

Java, C/C++, Python, Swift, PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, XML, ARM, System Verilog, MATLAB, TensorFlow, React, NodeJS, GitHub, Docker, AWS

Education

University of California

- San Diego

Sept 2018 – June 2022 B.S.: Computer Engineering Minor in Cognitive Science GPA 3.8

About me

Assistant Judo Instructor
Pianist and Ballroom Dancer
Ex-Military Paramedic
Native German speaker

3rd year Computer Engineering & Cognitive Science student at University of California – San Diego. Worked on embedded systems for vital functions of \$200,000 rocket. Performed large-scale data analysis used by the Austrian government. Social Computing Researcher.

Work History

2021-01 - current	Percipio, Maribor, Slovenia Business Analyst, Salesman Revise Business Model and Marketing strategy Pitch and sell to potential customers in US
2020-09 - current	 Protolab, La Jolla, CA Research Assistant, Designer, Software Engineer Research and design novel data-discussion-system Discuss progress in weekly meetings with professors Currently working on first prototype in NodeJS
2019-07 - 2019-08	ISHAP CARD, Vienna, Austria Analyst Intern Invented own predictive risk model to identify scammer companies Wrote Python/PHP that automatically visualized 200+ Austrian companies Findings presented to clients and Federal Ministry of Finance
2018-09 - 2019-06	Rocket Propulsion Laboratory, La Jolla, CA Avionics Software Engineer Implemented self-engineered communication protocols in Java/C for \$200,000 rocket Communicated ideas to 40+ team members and

Projects

see my website for more

2020	Trumpagotchi iOS-App – released on AppStore
2020	Covid iOS-App – Project Manager of 11 students
2019	Automized Olive Moment Detection - TensorFlow
2018	8 Bit Breadboard Computer – As simple as possible

thoroughly documented all work